

About

Hi! I'm Doan Dang Phu Vinh - QA Engineer,

As a tester with more than 4 years of experience in Automation and Manual testing, I want to dedicate myself to company projects, ensure projects are delivered with the best quality.

Basic Information

YEAR OF BIRTH:

EMAIL: ddphuvinh.1994@gmail.com

 PHONE:
 +84-335-750-145

 ADDRESS:
 Ho Chi Minh City

 LANGUAGE:
 VietNam, English

Professional Skills

MANUAL TESTING	80%	AUTOMATION TESTING WITH JAVA/ CUCUMBER / JUNIT	70%
PERFORMANCE TESTING/JMETER	70%	API TESTING	60%
BASIC KNOWLEDGE OF DATABASE/ SQL TESTING	60%	BUG TRACKING/JIRA	80%

Work Experience

IOV 2022 - FEB 2023

SAMSUNG PROJECT

Middle - Senior QC Automation Engineer.

- Participate in full Test Activities (Test Planning, Test Monitoring & Control, Test Analysis, Test Design, Test Implementation, Test Execution, Test Completion)
- Fully understand business requirements and products under testing.
- Collaborate with team members to ensure that requirements are met.
- Validation ensures the product under development is as per the User Story /User requirements.
- Identify, record, and document all bugs with bug tracking software using JIRA.
- $\ \, \text{Build/Developing \& Report Test Automation scripts using JAVA/CUCUMBER/JUNIT FRAMEWORK}.$
- Build Performance Testing using Jmeter.

JUNE 2021 - OCT 2022

METANET VIETNAM

Middle - Senior QC Engineer.

- Analysis requirements/ Design & Execute Test Levels (Component, Integration, System, Acceptance testing...)
- Participate in full Test Activities (Test Planning, Test Monitoring & Control, Test Analysis, Test Design, Test Implementation, Test Execution, Test Completion)
- Fully understand business requirements and products under testing
- Validation ensures the product under development is as per the user requirements
- Identify, record, and document all bugs with bug tracking software
- Build/ Developing & Report Test Automation scripts using JAVA/ CUCUMBER / JUNIT FRAMEWORK
- Build Performance Testing using Jmeter

JUNE 2017 - MAY 2021

DVC METNAM

QC Engineer

- Design and execute testcases, scenarios, scripts and procedures for testing on software applications.
- Identify software failures to flag and diagnose defects
- Designing and developing test automation scripts using DXC testing framework
- Fully understand business requirements and products under testing

Parelalanes in emission maneralan 0 sanables anti-def-

Participate in training, mentoring a coaching activitie

Education

Software Engineering
HOA SEN UNIVERSITY
Studied software engineering at Hoa Sen University
GPA: 2.8

PHP Developer
T3H.VN
Join the training program for PHP programmers
GPA: 3.4

TOEIC Certificate

TOEIC Certificate with 775 points